Kageyama Shigeo, also known as Mob.
A second-year in middle school.
The second year of middle school kicks off
the most sensitive period in one's life.
People call it adolescence.
Some hone their bodies playing sports,
some work hard on their studies,
some devote themselves to their hobbies,
some polish their talents,
some rebel,
and some fall for the opposite sex
and get a taste of bittersweet love.
All those youthful desires come together to
form the amalgamation that is adolescence.
And Mob was spending
that precious time working as
an assistant at a psychic business
for 300 yen an hour.
The reason is porn sites!
Porn sites...?
Yes! The curse that is on your shoulder is
a terrible one-click curse!
A terrible one-click curse!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%, 6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27%, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37%, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Mob Psycho 100" 91%, 92%, 93%,
94%, 95%, 96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Doubts About Youth"
"~The Telepathy Club Appears~"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
A-A one-click curse from porn sites?
They use illegal 18+ sites
to curse your shoulder
and make you pay fees.
Nowadays, even curses are being digitized.
Who the hell would believe that hogwash?
Just don't move for a second.
I'll lift the curse now.
No, it's fine!
Your right shoulder is stiff--
The curse is strong.
Hey! I'm not paying for this. Sto--
H-Huh? It actually feels good?
Sorcery Crush!
"Sorcery Crush"
It's finished!
This is one of Reigen's special moves,
"Abeshi"
"Abeshi" where he relieves
the stress from physical fatigue
"Abeshi"
"Abeshi" and gets rid of
stiff shoulders and back pain.
And gets rid of
I believe that I was able
to lift the curse,
but do your shoulders still feel heavy?
I'm sorry that I doubted you.
I feel much better!
May I come again?
Of course!
"Reception” "Manual” “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee
on 1 of them will be on the house!I" "This Month Only" Of course!
"Reception” "Manual” “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism
fee on 1 of them will be on the house!I" "This Month Only"
"Reception” "Manual” “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on
1 of them will be on the house!I" "This Month Only" Er, the massage fee
"Reception” "Manual” “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism
fee on 1 of them will be on the house!I" "This Month Only"
"Reception” "Manual” “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on 1 of them
will be on the house!I" "This Month Only" for the 40-minute course is 3,800 yen.
"Reception” "Manual” “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism
fee on 1 of them will be on the house!I" "This Month Only"
"Reception” "Manual” “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on 1 of them will be on the
house!I" "This Month Only" You idiot! Don't call it the massage fee! Call it the curse-dispelling fee!
You idiot! Don't call it the massage fee!
Call it the curse-dispelling fee!
Your change is 200 yen.
Here. You'll eat some, won't you, Mob?
Oh, sure. I'll have some.
Master Reigen, you're getting
much better at massages.
Well, yeah.
I've been trying various things to improve,
like reading books on Seitai.
"Limited-Time Offer" “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on 1 of them will be on the
house!I" "This Month Only" I've been trying various things to improve, like reading books on Seitaj.
"Limited-Time Offer" “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism
fee on 1 of them will be on the house!I" "This Month Only"
"Limited-Time Offer" “"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on 1 of them will be
on the house!I" "This Month Only" Of course, it's only effective because of spiritual power.
Of course, it's only effective
because of spiritual power.
Hot!
Such a waste!
Master, I've been thinking...
Well, this is rare.
You never try to start a conversation.
Well, I can use a little ESP,
and I'm different from other people,
so I came to discuss that with you
and ended up becoming your student.
At the time, I didn't have anyone else
to talk to, so I'm grateful,
because you teach me
various things and pay me.
However, is this really okay?
That's what I've been thinking lately.
Does he think his pay is too low?
"Fake" "Liar" "Con Artist"
"Self-Proclaimed Psychic"
"Fake" "Liar" "Con Artist" "Self-Proclaimed
Psychic" Or did he finally find me out?
Or did he finally find me out?
What do you mean?
How do I put this...?
Rather than waste my youth
working part-time after school,
I have a feeling
that there may or may not be
some other things that
I can only experience now...
Huh?
Oh, so that's it.
Such is puberty, Mob-kun.
Is there something that
you want to do right now?
Be in a band? Dance? Hitchhike?
"To Wakkanai"
"To Wakkanai" No, I don't
have anything particular in mind.
No, I don't have
anything particular in mind.
Listen, Mob. There's no need
to rush into things.
In my expert opinion,
the going-home club is the absolute best.
You're goofing off during the period
you can goof off the most,
and that makes you a winner in my book.
Keep on lazing around
and make money from me.
Got it?
Wait a sec, Takenaka!
I get treated like a weirdo
just for being in this club!
"Telepathy Club" I get treated like
a weirdo just for being in this club!
"Telepathy Club"
"Telepathy Club" --Just wait!
--I can't do it anymore!
--Just wait!
This isn't good.
A club must have five
or more members, right?
What should we do, President?
What else can we do?
We have to find new members
like our lives depend on it!
"Telepathy Club President: Kurata Tome" We have
to find new members like our lives depend on it!
"Telepathy Club President:
Kurata Tome"
Maybe Takenaka-san came back.
That's gotta be it! Takenaka!
"Student Council"
I just received a submission of resignation
from this club, so be forewarned...
The...
The student council!
"Student Council Vice President:
Tokugawa" The student council!
Tokugawa"
"Student Council Vice President:
Tokugawa" This club will now be abolished.
Tokugawa"
Abolished?
Already?!
Sadly, I'm going to have to ask you
to gather all of your things.
I actually just had a brand-new club
request a club room.
H-Hold your horses!
I'm not going to let you
abolish the Telepathy Club!
The Telepathy Club bond is strong.
The student council's got nothing on us!
You think you're all high-and-mighty
because of how you part your hair?!
Shut up. Do you really want to anger me?
If you're that desperate
to keep this club going,
bring me a new club member by
the end of the school day on Friday.
"Telepathy Club" bring me a new club member
by the end of the school day on Friday.
"Telepathy Club"
B-By Friday?
That only gives us two days.
That's impossible.
Quit whining!
If we ask everyone we see to join,
we'll be able to snag at least one!
No, that's impossible.
Recruiting season ended a long time ago.
No! I'm going to do this!
We have overcome so many obstacles
up until now, haven't we?!
President...
We haven't done a single thing...
"The Next Day After School"
Telepathy Club?
Sorry, what are you talking about?
--It's creepy, so no.
--I've got a job.
Abolished? What's wrong with that?
You should be studying.
We've got entrance exams this year.
Are there hot guys?
Do you have any hot guys?
I want to be able to date.
"Girls Bathroom"
"Girls Bathroom" I'd be worried about
the stares, and it seems dangerous.
"Girls Bathroom"
--It's creepy, so no.
--Sorry. It's creepy, so no.
It's creepy, so no.
--Creepy.
--No.
It's creepy, so no.
It really was impossible to find
new members this time of the year.
Not to mention we just
keep getting called creepy.
Now even I want to quit.
No!
The president's lost it!
Please calm down!
The going-home club...
President!
I've brought him!
He's not in any clubs or committees,
and he doesn't have
any friends or girlfriends.
Salt Middle's final go-homer
and all-round bum,
Kageyama Shigeo-kun of class 2-1.
Well, he's basically right.
Well done, Inukawa!
Let me introduce you to
the other members, Kageyama-kun.
This is Kijibayashi and Saruta.
--Nice to meet you.
--Hey.
And I'm the president,
Kurata Tome, from class 3-5.
Call me Tome-chan.
The president is pulling out all the stops!
Tome-chan...
That's my grandmother's name.
I-I'm sure that is fate's doing, too!
There you have it!
Join the Telepathy Club!
--I can't today.
--What?!
Wait a second, Mob!
You actually have plans?
Yeah. I have to go to my exorcism job now.
Exorcism? What's that supposed to mean?
Ah, President! Actually, this guy
was sort of famous in grade school.
He could bend spoons
and make erasers move...
In other words...
He's an esper!
Stop being weird and just join our club.
I'm sure the exorcism
can wait a little while.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
Hey, what's up, Mob?
Ah, Master.
Is it all right if I'm a little late today?
I'm being recruited into a club.
That should be over instantly.
No, I have to wait until
the student council meeting is over,
and then go submit
my club admission form.
Uh, wait. So if I tell you to come
immediately, you're not going to join?
Yes, well... Shouldn't I
keep the promise I made first?
So, it's not like you actually want to join?
Not really, no.
Then hurry on over.
Show them how quickly someone
in the going-home club can leave school.
He says he needs me right away,
so I'll be going now.
P-Put me on for a sec!
I really need Kageyama-kun
to join today, no matter what!
A girl, eh? She must be trying to use Mob.
Mob's not the type to play any sports.
Forcing him into things isn't good.
We're not a sports club!
We're the Telepathy Club!
Huh? What the hell is that?
It's a club where we train
to feel telepathic powers.
Uh, that sounds shady as hell.
What do you mean, "telepathy"?
Like you're one to talk!
I heard that Kageyama-kun has ESP.
Aren't you using that
to get more customers?
Because you're a phony!
Shut your mouth, amateur!
Don't you dare waste my student's
precious time with your nonsense!
What?!
Are you saying that you don't care
if our club gets abolished?
We'll get kicked out of the room!
Master, Senpai is about to cry,
so I think I'll join after all...
Don't be fooled!
Those are crocodile tears!
Bonds, memories, and friendship...
Like any of those things will disappear
because a club is abolished.
No! They just don't want
to lose their room, their budget,
and their pointless after-school time,
judging from what their club sounds like.
See through it, Mob!
That shady club is going down
because it's meant to go down.
If you understand,
hurry up and come to work!
I understand...
And so, I'll be leaving after all.
Wait! Hear me out, too!
It seems that the president
seriously believes in telepathy,
but honestly, yeah, I just want to goof off.
But, right now, we're in middle school.
This is the only time we're going
to be able to goof off!
Play cards with us in this
lazy little paradise we've created!
You're not going to find
a more carefree club than this.
We have until tomorrow, so think it over.
You're our last hope, Kageyama-kun!
You turned them down, didn't you?
No. I figured I could
take a night to think about it.
You shouldn't procrastinate, Mob.
You need to turn down things
you don't want to do.
Right now, the thing I least want to do
is be dressed like this.
Oh, there it is.
Saint Highso Girls' Academy.
It's a private all-girls high school.
We're meeting the clients up on the roof.
Okay.
"Highso Private Girls' Academy"
Stop! What are you doing?
Pardon?
"Highso Private Girls' Academy"
I'm talking to you! Don't play dumb!
I'm a student here.
Reporting from the front gate.
A suspicious individual showed up!
Requesting backup!
Hey, that's a bit mean, isn't it?
You perverted weirdo!
I knew this wouldn't work.
But I'm glad they instantly
saw through our disguises.
I didn't want to infiltrate the school
dressed up like this.
That was close, huh?
Now, hurry up and
get away from the pervert.
Huh?
We'll deal with this phony.
"GO"
Huh?
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 30%"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 31%"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 35%"
"Mob Psycho 100"
Won't I get in a lot
of trouble if I'm busted?
He said we were meeting on the roof, but...
Um, hello.
I've come from the consultation office.
Are you the clients?
Huh? Who the hell are you?
An unfamiliar face.
You a transfer student?
--Huh?
--Consultation office?
You trying to get through to us thugs?
So annoying!
Like we're going to let some
twerp like you lecture us!
--No, I'm just--
--Why don't you mind your own business?!
If you don't, you're going to regret it!
Sorry about that...
Man, talk about a downer. Let's go.
Hmph!
Hello?
You promptly got picked on
by thugs. How funny.
"Clients:" "Chihiro" "Mari" You promptly
got picked on by thugs. How funny.
"Clients:"
"Chihiro" "Mari"
"Clients:" "Chihiro"
"Mari" We're your clients.
"Clients:"
"Chihiro" "Mari"
Isn't that Reigen guy coming?
He was caught at the front gate.
Also, you both came here
dressed as girls? Seriously?
He couldn't get us permission to come in,
so we didn't have a choice...
I see.
Sorry to make you go through all that.
The school just refuses to take us seriously.
What did you tell them?
Students' belongings have been vanishing
under mysterious circumstances,
and we've been hearing weird noises...
Like, a poltergeist phenomenon?
We heard things have been spotted
floating through the air, too.
Right. Apparently a bra started
floating around in the locker room.
Bra...?
We're dead sure it has to be
something supernatural.
So we just called
the cheapest exorcist in the area
and somehow ended up with you.
Huh?
I can't believe a guy was trembling so much
dealing with some high school girls.
You must be quite the reliable gentleman.
Th-Thank you...
That was sarcasm, duh!
She wasn't complimenting you!
Are you sure we can trust you?
I have my doubts.
You seem unreliable.
--What?
--What's wrong?
I-It's okay...
I just have to perform an exorcism.
If you feel anything spiritual, let us know.
Right.
Well? Do you sense anything?
Just slightly...
I wonder if he's being serious...
It's here. Nearby.
Huh? Really?!
Someone help!
What's wrong?
Something was here...
Something was looking in
from the top of the door...
The windows are locked.
And no one's gone through the exit.
I'm going to follow the spirit.
Nothing so far?
We can trust you, right?
Right.
You still can't find it?
The spirit's angry.
Huh?
If we keep pursuing it,
it might try to do something.
Eek! What are we going to do?
The basketball team is practicing inside.
I'm going to end this.
I've trapped the spirit.
Pass! Pass! Hey!
I've found you.
Huh?
It's huge!
What is that?! A ghost?!
Psychic brat...
How dare you trap me?
Are you going to try to ruin my paradise?
"Evil Spirit: Scent-Ghoul"
This is what you get!
Crap. I underestimated the psychic.
If I don't take a hostage, he'll erase me!
You smell nice.
I choose you!
Look out!
Huh?
It's over.
--Wow. --Want to go home together today?
--How did you do that?
--What class is she in?
--So cool! --Tell me!
Listen to them cheer. Good for you.
Thanks. Looks like you were
pretty reliable after all.
Damn it...
How could I be defeated by a loser like you?
And here I thought
I'd finally found happiness.
You seem to be similar to me.
Similar?
The way you get nervous around girls...
You're playing the loser role in youth
just like me, aren't you?
I---
I finally started to have fun after I died.
I was content.
But I guess it's all over now.
Hey, are you living
every day to the fullest?
What's wrong?
You seem out of it.
Something troubling you?
Huh? No, I'm fine.
All right, then...
Mob!
You came!
We believed in you, Kageyama-kun!
Now, hurry up and
sign this club admission form.
You're already here?
That was awfully quick... Vice President!
Well, I had to show this room...
...to them.
This will become the club room
of the newly formed
Body Improvement Club.
What? Hold on a sec!
The Telepathy Club won't be abolished!
Kageyama-kun here is just about to join!
What?
--Are you insane?
--Huh?
--What grade are you in?
--I'm a second-year.
--Do you have any experience in other clubs?
--No.
--Do you have a close friend in the Telepathy Club?
--I have an acquaintance.
--Do you go to cram school?
--No.
--Do you study?
--Not really.
--Do you have any hobbies?
--Um...
--Don't you have anything that you want to do?
--Huh?
If you let them goad you into joining
despite having no interest at all,
what exactly will you gain from it?
Well, I just want to live
every day to the fullest.
And will wasting your time after school
with cola, snacks, and video games
help you do that?
If you want to join of your own
free will, I will not stop you.
However, you should
carefully reconsider this.
What is it that you really want to do?
What I want to do...
Do I have anything I want to do?
Does everyone else have something?
Something enjoyable?
Something I'm envious of?
What are they enjoying?
Clubs, hobbies, and studying?
Hanging out with girls might be fun...
I did have a dream!
I wanted to confess my feelings
to my first love, Tsubomi-chan,
and hold hands while walking home together.
Look, Tsubomi-chan.
When you make frogs float,
they start swimming.
Wow, how cute.
I can make the bar all squishy.
You're amazing, Mob-kun.
Look! I'm only showing you, Tsubomi-chan!
I'm bored of that.
The red team is fast!
You're so fast, Akira-kun!
That's right. If I can change
anything by joining a club...
I'll join!
Thank you for having me,
Body Improvement Club!
Huh? You want to join us?
Huh?
Good to have you!
Thank you!
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 40%" "Club Admission Form?" “"I
will join the Body Improvement Club.” "Class 2-1" "Kageyama Shigeo"
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light.
The dreams and ideals that we believe in
Feel like they may shatter
as soon as we take our eyes off them
Thousands, millions of distinct Flashbacks
Underneath the sky in slow motion,
So real that I want it to disappear.
My heart was stolen
a second before the unpredictable,
After being hurt on a whim
something from somewhere
is overflowing and won't stop.
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred?
We're looking for the answer.
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
"Yes n "No n
"Live" "Saint Highso Girls' Academy" "Pervert
Appears at an All-girls' School in Broad Daylight!!"
"Live" "Saint Highso Girls' Academy” "Pervert Appears at an All-girls'
School in Broad Daylight!!" Unable to locate the whereabouts
"Live" "Saint Highso Girls' Academy" "Pervert
Appears at an All-girls' School in Broad Daylight!!"
"Live" "Saint Highso Girls' Academy" "Pervert Appears at an All-girls' School in Broad
Daylight!!" of the suspicious individual who tried to infiltrate an all-girls' school
of the suspicious individual who tried
to infiltrate an all-girls' school
in broad daylight by cross dressing,
the whole area is on high alert...
Hot!
"Wakusen Newspaper" "Cross
dressing..." "Pervert!!" Hot!
"Wakusen Newspaper"
"Cross dressing..." "Pervert!!"
Mob successfully joins
the Body Improvement Club.
On his way home,
in an attempt to be popular,
he heads to the main temple
of an obviously shady-looking cult.
Are you really sure about this, Mob?
Next time, on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 3:
"An Invite to a Meeting
- Simply Put, I Just Want to be Popular~."
"An Invite to a Meeting"
"~Simply Put, I Just Want to be Popular~"
"An Invite to a Meeting" "~Simply Put, I Just Want to
be Popular~" Recording it? That's also a wise decision.